themadnews.com 2011-02-09

# Privacy Policy | The Mad News

## Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy** for _www.themadnews.com_

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at Admin@themadnews.com.

At www.themadnews.com, the privacy of our visitors is of Very importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.themadnews.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like most of the websites around, we collect and use the data store in log files. The information in the log files may include your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site , the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on www.themadnews.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes  or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.themadnews.com.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.themadnews.com and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include, Google Adsense

You can always chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings and with the use of  using preferences in programs of Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.
